briefing.com 2019-02-25

# 

                                      Privacy Statement
Effective on April 20, 2018
Privacy rights are a vital part of Briefing.com’s relationship with our readership. Towards
that goal this privacy statement is intended to communicate:
    1.  What personal information Briefing.com collects.
    2.  What personal information third parties collect through the Briefing.com website.
    3.  What organization collects the information.
    4.  How Briefing.com uses the information.
    5.  With whom Briefing.com may share user information.
    6.  What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of
        the information.
    7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or
        alteration of information under Briefing.com's control.
    8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Please note specifics of our Privacy Statement may change from time to time. If readers
have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact our Chief Privacy
Officer, Travis Rath, at cpo@briefing.com.
Definitions
This Privacy Statement relates to information collected by Briefing.com, Inc. (referred to
in this statement as “Briefing,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) through your use of our website and
your direct contact with us.
“You” or “your” refers to the individual who uses this website, receives information from
us, or directly contacts us.
As used in this Privacy Statement, the terms "using" and "processing" information
include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other
analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to
collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and
transferring information within our organization.
Types of Information Collected
Briefing.com collects two types of information: “personal information” and “non-personal
information.”
                                                                                           1

“Personal information” identifies you or may be used in combination with other pieces of
personal information to identify you. Examples of personal information include your
name, company name, job title, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and billing
and credit card information. Personal information can also include information that does
not identify you but could be combined with other information in a way that enables you
to be identified. This includes information such as age, gender, profession, zip code, IP
address, and current location.
“Non-personal information” is information that cannot be used or combined with other
information to identify or contact you, including browser types, domain names, and
statistical data.
Sources of Information
Briefing.com collects information from the following types of individuals:
Visitors to our website and users of our website, who may have non-personal
information collected through cookies on our website. For more information on how
cookies work and how to disable them, see our Cookie Policy.
    • Subscribers, and individuals who have expressed an interest in becoming
        subscribers, whose personal information is collected by Briefing.com during the
        signup process when voluntarily provided to us.
This policy first sets out how we collect, use, and store information obtained from
subscribers. It then sets out how we collect, use, and store information obtained from
visitors and users. Finally, we set out how information is shared and the rights you may
have in your information.
Collection and Use of Subscriber Information
Briefing.com collects personal information from subscribers when such information is
voluntarily provided to us, including through the Briefing.com registration process or
through direct contact with Briefing.com staff. This information is used to provide
subscribers with Briefing.com alerts, analysis, and promotional offers, or with support
services the subscriber has requested. Our practices are described in more detail
below.
Subscribers may also use cookies to enhance the functionality of the Briefing.com
website in a variety of ways, such as by allowing the Briefing.com website to remember
their login information. For more information on how cookies work and how to disable
them, please see our Cookie Policy.
Registration
Briefing.com’s free Investor service does not require registration of any kind. Any user is
free to access the Investor site without submitting any personal information.
                                                                                          2

Portions of the free Investor site require registration for access. We use the information
collected during the registration process to contact the registrant about services on our
site, including information provided as part of the subscription and special offers on
other Briefing.com services.
When signing up for premium services from Briefing.com, we ask for contact information
(such as name, email, and mailing address) and financial information (such as credit
card number and expiration date). This information is used to provide subscribers with
the requested services and for billing purposes. If we have trouble processing an order,
the information is used to contact the subscriber.
Communications from the Site
Special Offers and Updates
Out of respect for the privacy of our subscribers, we present the option to not receive
these types of communications. Please see the Account Settings sections of your
particular subscription for more information.
Newsletter
If a subscriber wishes to receive our newsletters, they must opt-in to receive them. In
order to provide our newsletters to subscribers who opt-in, we ask for contact
information, such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users’ privacy we
also provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Account
Settings sections of your particular subscription for more information.
Service Announcements
We send out service-related emails when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if we’re
experiencing technical difficulties or have implemented new enhancements to our
service, we may send an email notification. Generally, subscribers may not opt-out of
these communications. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to cancel
your account.
Customer Service
We send all new subscribers a confirmation email to verify their password and
username after registration. We also communicate with subscribers on a regular basis
to provide requested services as well as to notify subscribers of issues relating to their
account. We reply to communications from subscribers via email or phone, in
accordance with the user's preferences. Generally, users may not opt-out of these
communications. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to cancel your
account.
We also may contact subscribers or potential subscribers via email who have not
checked out, not completed registration, or abandoned forms to follow up and see if
there was problem with the process. You may opt-out of these communications at any
time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.
                                                                                           3

Storage of Subscriber information
Briefing.com stores information it collects from subscribers for as long as the
subscriber’s account is active. Credit card information is not stored by Briefing.com at
any time. Credit card information is stored and processed by a third party. We may also
retain subscriber information after a subscriber deactivates their account as necessary
to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations. We generally retain such information
for five years to facilitate reactivation of subscriber accounts. If you would like your
information to be deleted earlier, please contact Travis Rath at cpo@briefing.com.
Collection and Use of Visitor Information
We collect information from visitors to the Briefing.com website through the use of log
files, clear gifs, and cookies. In some cases, these technologies are provided by third
parties. This information is typically used for statistical analysis of our visitors, rather
than being used in a way that links the information collected with you individually.
If you are a subscriber, some information collected by these technologies may be
associated with your account to create a profile of your overall preferences when using
our site. This profile is used only by Briefing.com to help us improve your experience
with the Briefing.com website.
More detail is provided on our collection and use of visitor information in the sections
that follow.
Tracking Technologies
Technologies such as cookies, beacons, scripts and tags are used by Briefing.com and
our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in
analyzing trends, administering the website, tracking movements around the site, and
gathering demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive
reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual
and aggregated basis. To the extent that they collect personal information, these
companies will only use personal information for the purposes described in this section.
We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember subscriber settings (e.g. username),
and for authentication. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser
level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some
features or areas of our site may be limited. For more information about how cookies
are used on our site and how you may turn them off, visit our Cookie Policy.
Log Files
Like most websites, we use log files, which collect information about visitors to our
website for troubleshooting purposes only.
                                                                                             4

We do use third party providers to assist in analyzing usage of the site to better
understand how features are used, pages are visited and to then improve the services.
The data sent to our analytics partner includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser
type, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to
analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather
broad demographic information for aggregate use.
Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display
advertising based upon your web browsing activity cookies to track preferences. You
can disable ads and associated 3rd party cookies using various browser add-ins.
Do Not Track Requests
Briefing.com makes no response if a browser submits a "do not track" request. For
more information about how to limit how cookies are used on Briefing.com, see our
Cookie Policy.
Storage of Visitor Information
Much of the visitor information collected on Briefing.com is stored on the visitor’s device,
and Briefing.com does not control how long such information is stored. Visit our Cookie
Policy for information on how to delete cookies from your device. Subscriber profile
information is stored for as long as the subscriber’s account is active, or as necessary to
comply with our legal and regulatory obligations.
Sharing with Third Parties
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are
described below. Generally speaking, we share personal information in the following
cases:
    1. When a third-party intermediary collects or uses personal information on our
       behalf to provide services to subscribers or to provide Briefing.com with
       necessary business services;
    2. When a third-party advertiser collects information from visitors relating to
       browsing activity;
    3. When you share Briefing.com content on social media; and
    4. When such disclosure is required by law or other legal process.
Additionally, we may share your personal information if the ownership or business
structure of Briefing.com changes in the future.
Third Party Intermediaries
We use the following types of third party intermediaries:
    • an outside credit card processing company to bill subscribers for goods and
       services;
                                                                                           5

    •   marketing providers to provide visitors with information about our services and to
        notify potential subscribers who begin and then abandon the signup process that
        they may continue the process;
    • a secure contract processor to ensure that any documents that require your
        signature are signed securely; and
These companies do not retain, share, store or use personal information for any
purposes other than those listed above, and all of these third parties are contractually
obligated to treat your personal information with the same degree of care as
Briefing.com.
Third Party Advertisers
We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Website or to manage
our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partner may use technologies such as
cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to
provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. For
information about all of the cookies used on our website, you may visit our Cookie
Policy.
We also share aggregated demographic information with our advertisers. This
information is not linked to any identifiable individual.
Social Media Widgets
Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons
and Widgets or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may
collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to
enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either
hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these
Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.
Required Disclosures
Though we make every effort to preserve subscriber privacy, we may need to disclose
personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that
such action is necessary to comply with a law, regulation, current judicial proceeding,
court order, or legally binding request served on our Website.
Business Transitions
In the event Briefing.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being
acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, subscriber personal
information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Subscribers will be
notified via prominent notice on our Website for 30 days prior to a change of ownership
or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, personal
information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection,
subscribers will be given a choice consistent with our “Notification of Changes” section.
                                                                                             6

Links to Third Party Websites
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Briefing.com, are
not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our visitors
to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and
every website that collects personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to
information collected by Briefing.com.
Choice/Opt-out
Subscribers who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional
communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by managing their
email preferences within their service under Account Settings. Alternatively, all emails
have a "remove me" or "unsubscribe" link at the very bottom of the email which will
automatically remove the email address associated with that particular email offering or
allow the subscriber to unsubscribe. The subscriber may also contact us at 800-752-
3013 or 312-670-4463; service@briefing.com.
Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information
If your information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if you
no longer desire our services, we provide a way to correct, update or delete your
personal information or deactivate your account. This can be done by emailing our
Customer Support team at service@briefing.com. You may contact us by telephone at
the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within a
reasonable timeframe. Subscribers and visitors may also contact us to receive all of the
personal information Briefing.com holds about them. In some instances, such as when
we have already deleted a subscriber’s or visitor’s personal information, we will be
unable to provide a complete list of the personal information we have collected on a
given individual. To receive all personal information we have collected, please contact
Travis Rath at cpo@briefing.com.
Security
Briefing.com secures the personal information it stores using reasonable technical and
organizational security measures. All personal information stored by Briefing.com is
secured on remote servers provided by our third-party IT provider. Information regarding
the security of our servers is available on request by contacting us at the email address
listed below.
When we ask subscribers to enter financial information, that information is encrypted
and transferred to our third-party payment processor through a secure connection
                                                                                         7

Only employees who need access to personal information to perform a specific job, for
example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative, are granted access to
personal information.
We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to
us, both during transmission and once we receive it
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to
cpo@briefing.com.
Location of Data Storage
Briefing.com and its third-party providers store and process personal information in the
United States. By providing personal information to Briefing.com you consent to have
such personal information stored and processed in the United States.
For European Residents Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
Briefing.com collects and processes personal information relating to European data
subjects as prescribed in Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (also known as the General Data
Protection Regulation or the GDPR). The following terms describe our commitment to
our subscribers and visitors to process personal information consistent with the GDPR.
Briefing.com confirms that it transfers the data of European subscribers and visitors to
the United States for processing. Because Briefing.com is based in the United States,
this transfer is necessary in order for us to provide you with our website or services for
which you have subscribed. If you do not consent to the transfer of your data to the
United States, you must cease using the Briefing.com website and any services
provided by Briefing.com. We will update this privacy statement if at any time we begin
transferring data to another country.
In the event that you are unable to resolve a privacy-related complaint with us, you may
lodge a complaint with the data protection authority in your country.
You have additional rights under the GDPR, include a right to correct, receive, and
delete personal information we hold about you. Those rights are described above and
have been extended to all Briefing.com subscribers and visitors as a courtesy.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes to this privacy
statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are
always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what
circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the
privacy statement under which the information was collected.
                                                                                           8

If, however, we are going to use users' personal information in a manner different from
that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email prior to the change
becoming effective. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their
information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all
communication with the site, or deleted/ deactivated their account, then they will not be
contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if
we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user
information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our
Website notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will
also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of
the changes in our privacy practices prior to the change becoming effective.
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy statement, please
contact us at:
Phone: 800-752-3013 or 312-670-4463
Email: service@briefing.com
Postal Address: 401 N. Michigan Avenue, Suite 1910, Chicago, IL USA 60611
Website URL: www.briefing.com
If you are in the European Union then you may contact our designated representative
at:
ATTN: Briefing.com Data Protection Representative c/o Achieved Compliance
Advocacy Ltd.
Postal Address: 40 Oxford Road, High Wycombe, Buckinghamshire UK HP11 2EE
Email: briefing@gdprrepresentative.eu
Applicable Law
This privacy statement is governed by the laws of the state of Illinois, without regard to
its conflict of laws provisions.
                                                                                           9
